

JAGDEEP MATHARU

IOS ENGINEER

ABOUT

Self-taught iOS Engineer with 2 years of professional experience. Started my journey as Automation developer. Learned my way through and contributed to iOS apps based on EHR.

Created a Movie/TV app and worked as developer and designer - "myLinkReel"

SKILLS

Swift - Writing Swift for 2 years and have worked on multiple codebases in swift. Loved all.

Auto Layout - Experienced in building an adaptable UI for multiple screen sizes.

UI/UX Design - Passion for elegant and intuitive UI/UX. Took on the role of Designer at myLinkReel along with my Engineering duties.

EXPERIENCE

IOS SWIFT DEVELOPER • MYLINKREEL • OCT 2017 - CURRENT

IOS SWIFT DEVELOPER • POINTCLICKCARE / PRIVATE • AUG 2017 - CURRENT

INTERMEDIATE IOS AUTOMATION DEVELOPER • POINTCLICKCARE • NOV 2016 - CURRENT

AUTOMATION DEVELOPER • POINTCLICKCARE • AUG 2015 - OCT 2016

IT CONSULTANT • HOLTRENFREW • MAY 2015 - AUG 2015

SOFTWARE ENGINEER • BLACKBERRY • SEP 2013 - AUG 2014

JUNIOR DEVELOPER • PPR INFOTECH • DEC 2010 - MAY 2011

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING • MAY 2015 • CENTENNIAL COLLEGE

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN CS • MARCH 2012 • PTU

AERONAUTICAL ENGINNERRING • JULY 2009 • PAMEC







